markets well we're seeing some a little
bit of red action on the screen despite
a better better than expected earnings
before from PNG CEO John Mueller uh told
me the consumer is staying resilient in
the face of high inflation but
nonetheless right now we're seeing the
markets in the red now here's what's on
tap for you this hour here comes Tesla's
earnings our senior Auto correspondent
press subramanian tease up Tesla's
earnings for uh you uh as they are out
after the close the demand for faucets
Fortune brand CEO Nicholas Fink stops by
for an in-depth look into the building
products maker amid the housing market
slowdown and no recession that's a take
from Bank of America seal Brian Moynihan
in my chat with him just moments ago
we'll have that interview coming up Brad
over to you all right taking a look at
the major averages here as we've struck
the top of the 10 a.m hour 30 minutes
into trade and I want to give you a
three-day look at what's kind of taking
place here over the course of this week
even despite today's little blippity
blip we are seeing us hold on to a
three-day gain of about 2.8 percent here
for the Dow Jones Industrial Average the
NASDAQ composite you're seeing that hold
on to gains of about 3.7 percent over
that three-day period but here today
right now down by about six tenths of a
percent 35 minutes into trade also the S
P 500 you're seeing that lower on the
day that's down by about half a percent
we ran through some of the sectors
earlier but I'd love to shift your
attention over to retail as we're
keeping an eye on some of those names
especially within that consumer
discretionary construct or discussion
here and especially going into a holiday
season where we're still going to be
looking through Amazon Walmart and some
of these sales that are set to commence
that have already actually kicked off
Walmart actually announcing this morning
that they are not going to be open on
Thanksgiving that continues what we had
seen over some recent years as well in
2020 and 2021 and so keep a close eye on
these retail names Amazon down by about
1.7 Walmart down by about two tenths of
a percent Target also lower on the day
by about six tenths of a percent so
that's a retail Roundup if you will for
right now this is the top of the 10 a.m
hour Julie
whatever actually no we've got a guest
that's coming in although it may feel
like we're already in One Mini
economists still don't think the U.S
meets the formal definition of a
recession based on broader measures such
as income spending and job growth